In this video, we're gonna talk about static typing versus dynamic typing. One
在这段视频中，我们将讨论静电打字与动态打字的对比。一
way to think about the purpose of static types system is to prevent common
对静电类型制目的的思考是为了防止常见的
programming errors and they do this at compile times. So they do this when the
编程错误，它们在编译时这样做。所以他们这样做的时候
program is compiled. And in particular they do it without knowing any input to
编写了程序。具体地说，他们在不知道任何输入的情况下这样做
the program. So the only thing that is available is the program text, and that's
这个项目。所以唯一可用的就是程序文本，那就是
why we call them static Because they don't involve any of the dynamic behavior, the
为什么我们叫它们静电，因为它们不涉及任何动态行为，
actual execution behavior of the program. Now any type system that is correct, any
程序的实际执行行为。现在，任何正确的类型系统、任何
static type system that actually does the right thing, is going to have to disallow
静电类型的系统实际上做的是正确的事情，将不得不禁止
some correct programs. It can't reason completely precisely at compile time about
一些正确的程序。它不能在编译时完全准确地推论
everything that could happen as the program runs. Now what this means is that
程序运行时可能发生的一切。现在这意味着
some correct programs, by that I mean some programs that would actually run correctly
一些正确的程序，我的意思是一些实际可以正确运行的程序
if you executed them, are going to have to be disallowed by the type checker. And so
如果您执行了它们，类型检查器将不得不禁止。因此，
for this reason some people argue for a dynamic type checking instead, and this is
出于这个原因，有些人主张使用动态类型检查，这是
type checking that's done solely when the program runs. So at run time we check
仅在程序运行时执行的类型检查。所以在运行时我们检查
whether the actual operations were executing are appropriate for the actual
正在执行的实际操作是否适合于
data that arises when the program executes. Other people say well the
程序执行时产生的数据。其他人说得好
problem is really just that the type systems just aren't expressive enough and
真正的问题是类型系统没有足够的表现力，
we should work on fancier static type checking systems. And. Over time, there's
我们应该在更花哨的静电验型系统上下功夫。和。随着时间的推移，会有
been a considerable development in both camps. We see a lot of new dynamically
在两个阵营都是一个相当大的发展。我们动态地看到了很多新的
type checked languages, coming out, so a lot of the modern scripting like languages
输入检查语言，出来了，所以很多现代脚本都喜欢语言
and domain specific languages have some form of dynamic type checking. Other
领域特定语言具有某种形式的动态类型检查。其他
people have been working on fancier and fancier type systems and actually there's
人们一直在研究越来越花哨的类型系统，实际上
been a lot of progress, in static checking The disadvantage of the more expressive
有了很大进步，在静电查劣势更有表现力
text. Time checking systems they do tend to get more complicated though, and not
文本。不过，他们的时间检查系统往往会变得更加复杂，而不是
all of these features that these people have develop have actually found their way
这些人发展起来的所有这些特征实际上都找到了他们的方式
yet into main stream languages. Now , one important idea that this discussion
但仍被翻译成主流语言。现在，这场讨论的一个重要观点是
suggests is that there are two different notions of type. There is the dynamic
表明有两种不同的类型概念。这是一种动态
type. That is the type that the object or the value that we're talking about
键入。这就是我们正在讨论的对象或值的类型
actually has at run time And then there is the static type, which is the compile time
实际上在运行时有，然后是静电类型，这是编译时
notion, what the type checker knows about the object. And there is some relationship
概念，类型检查器知道关于对象的信息。其中有一些关系
that has to exist between the static type and the dynamic type if the static type
它必须存在于静电类型和动态类型之间(如果静电类型
checker is to be correct. In this relationship can be formalized by some
切克应该是正确的。在这个关系中可以用一些形式化为
kind of a theorem that proves something like the following, what we'd like to know
这是一个定理，它证明了如下内容，我们想知道的是
is that for every expression E, for every program expression E that you can write in
就是对于每个表达式E，对于你可以写进的每个程序表达式
the programming language, the static type that the compiler says that the, the
编程语言，编译器说的静电类型，
expression is going to have is equal to the dynamic type of that expression.
表达式的动态类型等于该表达式的动态类型。
Another way is saying that if you actually run the program. Then you get something
另一种说法是，如果你真的运行程序。然后你会得到一些东西
that is consistent with what you expected to get from the static type checker. That
这与您期望从静电类型检查器获得的结果是一致的。那
the static type checker is actually able to correctly predict what values will hap,
静电类型检查器实际上能够正确预测将发生什么值，
will, will arise at run time. And in fact in the early days of programming languages
将在运行时出现。事实上，在编程语言的早期
these were exactly the kinds of terms we had for the very simple type systems in
这些正是我们在中用来描述非常简单的类型系统的术语
the languages at that time. Now the situations a little more complicated for a
当时的语言。现在的情况有点复杂，对于一个
language like COOL. So let's take a look at the execution of a, a typical COOL
语言很酷。那么让我们来看看如何执行一个典型的酷
program. So here's a couple of classes, class A and a class B that inherits from
程序。这里有几个类，A类和B类，它们继承自
A. So B is going to be a subtype of A which we'll write like that. And now we
A，所以B将是A的一个子类型，我们这样写。现在我们
have a declaration here of X having type A and this is the static type of X. So the
这里声明X的类型为A，这是X的静电类型。
static type of X is A. And that's what the compiler knows about X's value. And then
静电类型的X是A，这就是编译器所知道的X的值。然后
here, when we execute this line of code, we can see that we assign a new A object
在这里，当我们执行这行代码时，我们可以看到我们分配了一个新的A对象
to X. And the fact that it's new is not important. All that's important is the
对X来说，它是新的这一事实并不重要。最重要的是
fact that it's an A object. And so, at this point, the dynamic type of X is also
它是一个A级物体的事实。因此，在这一点上，X的动态类型也是
A. Okay. So if this line of code when it actually execu tes A, which was declared
好的。所以如果这行代码在它实际执行时执行了A，它被声明为
to have static type A, actually holds an object of class A. But a little bit later
若要使静电类型为A，实际上持有的是A类的对象，但稍晚一点
on, down at this line of code, the dynamic type is actually different. The dynamic
在这行代码中，动态类型实际上是不同的。动感十足的
type here of X Is going to be B. K line of code executes x holds a b object even
这里X的类型将是B。k行代码执行x，甚至包含b对象
though it's declared Have a different type. And this is a very, very important
尽管它被声明为具有不同的类型。这是一个非常非常重要的
distinction to keep in mind. So there's a static type, there's a type that the
要牢记区别。所以有一种静电类型，有一种类型的
compiler knows about, and that's invariant. X has type A It always has type
编译器知道，这是不变的。X具有类型A，它始终具有类型
a All the uses of x for the entire scope of our typed with class A by the compiler.
在我们的整个作用域中，编译器使用类A类型化了x的所有用法。
But at run time, because we have assignments and we can assign different
但是在运行时，因为我们有赋值，并且我们可以分配不同的
objects to x, x can actually take on objects of different types, different run
x，x的对象实际上可以接受不同类型、不同运行的对象
time types. Type b, that's assigned x when the program executes.
时间类型。类型b，它在程序执行时分配给x。